Jascha Heifetz Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1911-1974 (Box 1-247)
  - Music Arranged and Edited by Jascha Heifetz (Box-folder 1/19-21, Box-folder 15/1, Box 2-14)
    - Composers
      - Dinicu, Grigoras
        - Hora staccato, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-saxophone score (Box-folder 5/12)
        - Hora staccato, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-saxophone score (Box-folder 5/12)
        - Hora staccato, Printed piano-saxophone score and part (Box-folder 5/12)
        - Hora staccato, Ms. orchestral score (Box-folder 6/1)
        - Hora staccato, Photostat of ms. parts (Box-folder 6/1)
        - Hora staccato, Ms. full score (Box-folder 242/1)
        - Hora staccato, Ms. full score (revised) (Box-folder 242/2)
        - Hora staccato, Printed orchestral parts (Box-folder 6/2)
        - Hora staccato, Printed solo accordion score; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 6/3)
        - Hora staccato, Printed duet accordion score (Box-folder 6/4)
        - Hora staccato, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 6/5)
        - Hora staccato, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 6/5)
        - Hora staccato, Printed 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 6/5)
        - Hora staccato, Piano-viola score and part (Box-folder 6/6)
        - Hora staccato, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano score (Box-folder 6/7)
        - Hora staccato, Printed piano score (Box-folder 6/7)
        - Hora staccato, Piano score and dance orchestra parts (Box-folder 7/1)
        - Hora staccato, Piano-trumpet score and part (Box-folder 7/2)
        - Hora staccato, Piano score (simplified version) (Box-folder 7/3)
        - Hora staccato, Piano score and band parts (Box-folder 7/4)
        - Hora staccato, Piano-xylophone score and part (Box-folder 7/5)
        - Hora swingcato, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) sketches; Laid in: lyric sheet (Box-folder 7/6)
        - Hora swingcato, Ms. sketches (Box-folder 7/6)
        - Hora swingcato, Photostat of ms. piano-vocal score (Box-folder 7/6)
        - Hora swingcato, Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 7/6)
        - Hora swingcato, Printed full score (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Drigo, Richard
        - Valse bluette, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 7/7)
        - Valse bluette, Piano score (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Dvořák, Antonin
        - Humoreske, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 7/9)
        - Humoreske, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 7/9)
        - Humoreske, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 7/9)
      - Elgar, Edward
        - La capricieuse, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Fauré, Gabriel
        - Aubade, Negative photostat of holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 7/11)
        - [Soir, op. 83, no. 2], Negative photostat of holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Foster, Stephen
        - Jeanie with the light brown hair, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/1)
        - Jeanie with the light brown hair, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/1)
        - Jeanie with the light brown hair, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 8/1)
        - Old Folks at home, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/2)
        - Old Folks at home, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/2)
        - Old Folks at home, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Gershwin, George
        - [Porgy and Bess. Selections], Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/3)
        - [Porgy and Bess. Selections], Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/3)
        - [Porgy and Bess. Selections], Printed piano-violin scores and parts; Includes: Summertime & a woman is a sometime thing (2) Tempo di blues [There's a boat dat's leavin' soon for New York] (2) My man's gone now (2) It ain't necessarily so (2) Bess, you is my woman (2); Selections from Porgy and Bess, Russian edition (Box-folder 8/3)
        - [Preludes, piano], Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/4)
        - [Preludes, piano], Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/4)
        - [Preludes, piano], Printed piano-violin score and part; Various editions (4) (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Glazunov, Alexander
        - [Meditation, op. 32], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Gluck, Christoph Willibald von
        - Ballet Music, Photostat and negative photostat of holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/6)
        - Sonata, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/7)
        - Sonata, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/7)
        - Sonata, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Godowsky, Leopold
        - Alt-Wien, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score, in pencil (Box-folder 8/8)
        - Alt-Wien, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score, in ink (Box-folder 8/8)
        - Alt-Wien, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Gounod, Charles
        - Ave Maria, Printed piano-violin score and part with alterations to violin part by Heifetz; Heifetz holograph alternative 31 bars of violin part on verso of printed violin part (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Halffter, Ernesto
        - Danza de la gitana, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 8/10)
        - Danza de la gitana, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Handel, George Frederic; Johan Halvorsen
        - Passacaglia, Printed violin and viola parts, marked "score" on cover (Box-folder 9/1)
        - Passacaglia, Printed violin part with alterations by Heifetz, marked "1st violin" on cover (Box-folder 9/1)
        - Passacaglia, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) violin part with heading "Passacaglia" (for 2 violins); On cover: "2nd violin" (Box-folder 9/1)
        - Passacaglia, Photocopies (2) of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) violin part with heading "Passacaglia" (for 2 violins); On cover: "2nd violin" (Box-folder 9/1)
        - Passacaglia, Printed viola part with alterations by Heifetz (Box-folder 9/1)
        - Passacaglia, Printed cello part with alterations by Heifetz (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Haydn, Franz Joseph
        - Adagio and presto, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 9/2)
        - Adagio and presto, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Hummel, Johann Nepomuk
        - Rondo in E-flat major, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 9/3)
        - Rondo in E-flat major, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Ibert, Jacques
        - [Histiores. Le petit âne blanc], Photostat of holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Khachaturian, Aram
        - Ayshe's dance, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 9/5)
        - Ayshe's dance, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 9/5)
        - Sabre Dance, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 9/6)
        - Sabre Dance, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Krein, Alexander
        - Dance (No. 4), Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 9/7)
        - Dance (No. 4), Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 9/7)
        - Dance (No. 4), Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Kreisler, Fritz
        - [Quartet, strings. 3rd movement], Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin I-violin II score (Box-folder 9/8)
        - [Quartet, strings. 3rd movement], Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) violin parts (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Kroll, Louis
        - Perpetual motion, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Lavallée, Calixa
        - O Canada, Printed piano-vocal score with alterations to piano part by Heifetz (Box-folder 9/10)
        - O Canada, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) violin part adapted from original vocal parts (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Löhr, Herman
        - Where my caravan has rested, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) violin part; With:Lullaby/ Benjamin Godard (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Medtner, Nicolai
        - Fairy Tale, op. 20, no. 1, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 9/12)
        - Fairy Tale, op. 20, no. 1, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 9/12)
        - Fairy Tale, op. 20, no. 1, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) violin part (Box-folder 9/12)
        - Fairy Tale, op. 20, no. 1, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Mendelssohn, Felix
        - On wings of song, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 9/13)
        - Sweet remembrance, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 9/14)
        - Scherzo, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/1)
        - Scherzo, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/1)
        - Scherzo, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 10/1)
        - Scherzo, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/2)
        - Scherzo, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/2)
        - Scherzo, Printed piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Milhaud, Darius
        - Modéré, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/3)
        - Modéré, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/3)
        - Modéré, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 10/3)
        - Braziliera, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/4)
        - Braziliera, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/4)
        - Braziliera, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Moszkowski, Moritz
        - Guitarre, op. 45, no. 2, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
        - Divertimento, K. 287, B-flat major, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/6)
        - Divertimento, K. 287, B-flat major, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 10/6)
        - Divertimento, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/7)
        - Divertimento, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/7)
        - Divertimento, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 10/7)
        - Menuet, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 10/8)
        - Menuetto, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/9)
        - Menuetto, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/9)
        - Menuetto, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 10/9)
        - Menuetto, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/10)
        - Menuetto, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 10/10)
        - Menuetto, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 10/10)
        - Allegro molto, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/1)
        - Allegro molto, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/1)
        - Allegro molto, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 11/1)
      - Paradis, Maria Theresa von
        - Toccata, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/2)
        - Toccata, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 11/2)
      - Ponce, Manuel
        - Estrellita, Ms. piano-vocal score on Ditson music paper; Lyric sheet laid in (Box-folder 11/3)
        - Estrellita, Ms. piano-vocal score on Lyric music paper (Box-folder 11/3)
        - Estrellita, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Popper, David
        - Fileuse, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Poulenc, Francis
        - Mouvements Perpétuels, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/5)
        - Mouvements Perpétuels, Printed piano-violin score and part; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 11/5)
        - Presto, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/6)
        - Presto, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/6)
        - Presto, Photostat of holograph annotated by Poulenc (Box-folder 11/6)
        - Presto, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 11/6)
        - Promenade a Pied, Negative photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Prokofiev, Sergei
        - Le Marchand amoureux, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/8)
        - Le Marchand amoureux, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/8)
        - Le Marchand amoureux, Negative photostat of holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/8)
        - Le Marchand amoureux, Printed piano-violin score and part; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 11/8)
        - March and promenade from music for children, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/9)
        - March and promenade from music for children, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) violin part of March (Box-folder 11/9)
        - March and promenade from music for children, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 11/9)
        - March from the opera love for three oranges, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/10)
        - March from the opera love for three oranges, Photostat and negative photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/10)
        - March from the opera love for three oranges, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 11/10)
        - March, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/11)
        - March, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/11)
        - March, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 11/11)
        - Gavotta, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/12)
        - Gavotta, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 11/12)
        - Masks from "Romeo and Juliette", Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/13)
        - Masks from "Romeo and Juliette", Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 11/13)
        - Masks from "Romeo and Juliette", Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 11/13)
        - Larghetto and gavotta, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violn score (Box-folder 12/1)
        - Larghetto and gavotta, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Rachmaninoff, Sergei
        - Daisies, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 12/2)
        - Etude-Tableau, op. 33, no. 2, G minor, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/3)
        - Etude-Tableau, op. 33, no. 2, G minor, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/3)
        - Etude-Tableau, op. 33, no. 2, G minor, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 12/3)
        - Etude-Tableau, op. 33, no. 7, E-flat major, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/4)
        - Etude-Tableau, op. 33, no. 7, E-flat major, Photostat and ozalid of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/4)
        - Etude-Tableau, op. 33, no. 7, E-flat major, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 12/4)
        - Etude-Tableau, op. 33, no. 8, G minor, Negative photostat of holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/5)
        - Melody, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/6)
        - Melody, Photostats (2) and negative photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/6)
        - Melody, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 12/6)
        - Oriental Sketch, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/7)
        - Oriental Sketch, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/7)
        - Oriental Sketch, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 12/7)
        - [Prelude, op. 23, no. 9, E-flat minor], Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/8)
        - [Prelude, op. 23, no. 9, E-flat minor], Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/8)
        - [Prelude, op. 23, no. 9, E-flat minor], Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 12/8)
        - [Prelude, op. 32, no. 5, G major], Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/9)
        - [Prelude, op. 32, no. 5, G major], Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/9)
        - [Prelude, op. 32, no. 5, G major], Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 12/9)
        - Andante, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/10)
        - Andante, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) violin part (Box-folder 12/10)
        - It's peaceful here, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/11)
        - It's peaceful here, Photostat and negative photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/11)
        - It's peaceful here, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Rameau, Jean Philippe
        - Rigaudon, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/12)
        - Rigaudon, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 12/12)
        - Tambourin, Edited version of free transcription by Joseph Achron (Box-folder 12/13)
        - Tambourin, Arranger's holograph (Achron?) piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 12/13)
        - Tambourin, Printed piano-violin score and part; Edited by Heifetz (Box-folder 12/13)
      - Ravel, Maurice
        - Prelude, Negative photostat of holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/14)
        - [Le Tombeau de Couperin. forlane], Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/15)
        - [Le Tombeau de Couperin. forlane], Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 12/15)
        - [Le Tombeau de Couperin. forlane], Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 12/15)
        - Valses nobles et sentimentales, no. 6, no. 7, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/1)
        - Valses nobles et sentimentales, no. 6, no. 7, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/1)
        - Valses nobles et sentimentales, no. 6, no. 7, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolai
        - Flight of the bumblebee, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Rouget de Lisle, Claude Joseph
        - Le Marseillaise, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Saenger, Gustav
        - Intermezzo Scherzoso, Original printed piano-violin score and part; Extensive alterations by Heifetz (Box-folder 13/4)
        - Intermezzo Scherzoso, Printed piano-violin score and part with Heifetz as editor (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Saint-Saëns, Camille
        - The Swan, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/5)
        - The Swan, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/5)
        - The Swan, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Sarasate, Pablo de
        - Malagueña, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 13/6)
        - Zapateado, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Scarlatti, Domenico
        - Sonatina, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/8)
        - Sonatina, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 13/8)
        - Twelve selected pieces, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/9)
        - Twelve selected pieces, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/9)
        - Twelve selected pieces, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Schubert, Franz
        - Ave Maria, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 13/10)
        - Impromptu, op 90, no. 3, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/11)
        - Impromptu, op 90, no. 3, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/11)
        - Impromptu, op 90, no. 3, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 13/11)
      - Schumann, Robert
        - Prophetic bird, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Sibelius, Jean
        - Nocturne, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 13/13)
      - Smith, John Stafford
        - Star spangled banner, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/14)
        - Star spangled banner, Photostats of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (2) (Box-folder 13/14)
      - Strauss, Richard
        - Dream in the twilight, Negative photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/15)
        - Along the silent forest path, Negative photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/16)
      - Stravinsky, Igor
        - Suite italienne, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Gregor Piatigorsky) violin-cello score; Alterations to photostat by Heifetz (Box-folder 13/17)
      - Turina, Joaquin
        - Oración del Torero, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 14/1)
        - Oración del Torero, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 14/1)
        - Oración del Torero, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Valle, F.
        - Ao pé da fogueira, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 14/2)
        - Ao pé da fogueira, Photostat of arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 14/2)
        - Ao pé da fogueira, Printed piano-violin score and part (3) (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Vivaldi, Antonio
        - Larghetto, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 14/3)
        - Larghetto, Printed piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Waxman, Franz
        - [Carmen Fantasie; arr.], Holograph violin part; Extensive alterations by Heifetz (Box-folder 14/4)
        - [Carmen Fantasie; arr.], Holograph (Heifetz); Labelled "Carmen fantasy" (Box-folder 14/4)
        - [Carmen Fantasie; arr.], Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Weber, Carl Maria von
        - Rondo, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 14/5)
        - Rondo, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Wieniawski, Henryk
        - Caprice, Arranger's holograph (Heifetz) piano-violin score (Box-folder 14/6)
        - Caprice, Printed piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Collections
      - Favorite encore folio, Piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 14/7)
      - New favorite encore folio, Piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 14/8)
      - P'esy Frantsuzskikh kompozitorov, Piano-violin score and part; Pieces by Russian composers (Box-folder 14/9)
      - P'esy Russkikh kompozotorov, Piano-violin score and part; Pieces by Russian composers (Box-folder 15/1)